

### **Bachelor in Computer Science, Assistant Research Scientist**

I am an Assistant Research Scientist in the Security and Trust unit at FBK. I joined the S&T unit to explore and improve TLS analysis and delve into identity management. I am working concurrently between FBK and the Istituto Poligrafico e Zecca dello Stato.

# **Experiences**

## Fondazione Bruno Kessler (Trento, Italy)

Assistant Research Scientist • Feb., 2021 - Present

Security analysis of the TLS deployments of IPZS projects, TLS Analysis in Android Apps and TLS tool enhancement within the Security & Trust research unit.

*Internship* • *Feb, 2020 - May, 2020* 

Study and improvement of TLS analysis tools within the Security & Trust research unit.

**Projects** 

#### **TLSAssistant**

Version 1.3 and 2.0 (soon) • 2020 - Present

Fully-featured tool that combines state-of-the-art TLS analyzers with a report system that suggests appropriate mitigations and shows the full set of viable attacks.

#### iHash

Perceptual hashing library in python • 2020 - Present

Python library to easily check if two images are similar without machine learning by using Perceptual Hashing (phash and whash combined), with ban and unban image system.

## **Minor Works**

#### **Mallodroid**

Conversion in Python 3 and enhancements • 2020 - 2021

## telegram-deep-fakes-bot

Easy implementation and use of the first order model • 2020

## <u>Rappresentanti Bot</u>

HelpDesk Telegram bot to support DISI Students in University of Trento ● 2019

# **Education**

## **University of Trento (Trento, Italy)**

Bachelor of Computer Science • Sept, 2017 - Mar, 2021

Thesis in TLS Analyzers for Android Apps - State-of-the-art Analysis and Integration in TLSAssistant

## I.I.S. Primo Levi (Badia Polesine, Italy)

High School Diploma • Sept, 2012 - Sept, 2017

Final elaborate in psychoanalysis of James Joyce and the artificial intelligences

# Certifications

#### **First Certificate**

Cambridge Assessment English - B2 ● Apr, 2017

#### **ECDL Base**

ECDL / ICDL Certification • May, 2016



